const easy = [
  {
    question: "What country owns every panda in the world?",
    answers: {
      a: "China",
      b: "Japan",
      c: "Korea",
      d: "Australia"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },

  {
    question: "Lucy in the sky with __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Sunshine",
      b: "Diamonds",
      c: "Stars",
      d: "Rockets"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was tested at \"Bikini Atoll\" in the 1940's and the 1950's?",
    answers: {
      a: "Nuclear bomb",
      b: "Atomic bomb ",
      c: "Stealth aircraft",
      d: "Mustard gas"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which atmospheric gas is the most common?",
    answers: {
      a: "Hydrogen",
      b: "Oxygen",
      c: "Argon",
      d: "Nitrogen"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Excuse me while I __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Eat this pie",
      b: "Kiss this guy",
      c: "Kiss the sky",
      d: "Go mile high"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },

  {
    question:
      'Which star of the film "Rebel Without a Cause" died at the age of 24?',
    answers: {
      a: "James Dean",
      b: "Natalie Wood",
      c: "Gregory Peck",
      d: "Clark Gable"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic flag's colors are always red, black, blue, green, and yellow rings on a field of white because __:",
    answers: {
      a:
        "At least one of those colors appears on the flag of every nation on the planet.",
      b: "They are primary colors.",
      c: "They have important symbolism.",
      d: "Each color is owned by the United States."
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Wooly Mammoths were still alive when __:",
    answers: {
      a: "The Mayan calendar began.",
      b: "Barley and wheat were first cultivated.",
      c: "The Great Pyramid of Giza was built.",
      d: "The Bronze Age began."
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: 'Who wrote "Where the Sidewalk Ends?"',
    answers: {
      a: "Allen Ginsberg",
      b: "Charles Bukowski",
      c: "Dr Seuss",
      d: "Shel Silverstein"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },

  {
    question: '"Psycho" was the first American film to show __:',
    answers: {
      a: "Gory murder scenes",
      b: "A psychopath",
      c: "A flushing toilet",
      d: "Matricide"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  }
];
